https://www.aliensthetruth.com/privacy-policy/

Last updated: 1/22/2016
This privacy policy applies to all visitors to the AliensTheTruth.com website, www.aliensthetruth.com.
This privacy policy describes how we use and share personal information that we collect on our website.
This policy does not apply to third parties that AliensTheTruth.com does not own or control.
AliensTheTruth.com does not knowingly collect personal information about children. If we are made aware that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.
What information do we collect?
AliensTheTruth.com automatically collects and stores certain types of information provided by web browsers when visitors interact with the AliensTheTruth.com website. This information is automatically provided by the web browser to websites and includes such information as the visitor's IP address, the URL requested, and interactions with the AliensTheTruth.com website.
How we use information we collect
AliensTheTruth.com uses the information we collect to improve the performance and usability of our website.
How we share information we collect
AliensTheTruth.com does not share any information we collect with any third parties.
Third party links and services
AliensTheTruth.com may link to third party websites.
AliensTheTruth.com is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third party websites.
Visitors should check the privacy policy of any third party website AliensTheTruth.com links to.
Cookies and Web beacons
AliensTheTruth.com does not employ the use of cookies or web beacons.
Third party ad networks
AliensTheTruth.com does not employ the use of any third party ad networks.
California privacy
If you visit AliensTheTruth.com and you reside in California and you provide any personal information to AliensTheTruth.com, you may request a list of any third parties that we have shared your personal information with. You can make one such request per calendar year.
If you make such a request, please state that you are a California resident and provide your current address.
You may request this information by emailing us at:
Privacy Policy updates
AliensTheTruth.com may make changes to this privacy policy from time to time. Notice will be provided on this page whenever any material changes have been made to the policy.
About Us
We are dedicated to providing information on UFO sightings, alien incidents, world mysteries, and other paranormal activity.
There are so many cases where governments, individuals, or groups of people are involved in incidents involving an aliens or UFOs. Some instances have been very well publicized while others have not. We believe that given the incredible frequency with which alien/UFO sightings occur that there is a distinct possibility that extraterrestrial life exists. It is up to individuals to try and get governments to release the information they have on UFOs/aliens. The truth is out there!
Contact
Please feel free to contact us with any questions or comments you may have about our website. We can be reached via email at the following address:
Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2016 AliensTheTruth.com
